last 18 hours now. How's it been?
>> Excited. Excited. Um, been chilling with
the family, celebrating this moment. Um,
me and AJ just been laughing, enjoying
it. Especially me and him. We done, we
done hug each other about 20 times.
>> For real. So, it's been good though.
>> It can't feel real, right? Like,
>> yeah.
>> You again.
>> It's crazy. Like,
that's I didn't think it was gonna
happen. I didn't think it was gonna
happen. I'm glad it happened. I'm glad
it happened. They made a mistake letting
me and my bro team up.
>> They weren't supposed to let that
happen.
>> What What did you think was going to
happen? Did you have a sense of like,
"Oh, this team likes me or I'll probably
go in this framed or or anything like
that."
>> Um, yeah, I did. But, you know, God's
playing. I was playing. I got picked up
by a team that wanted me. And I
appreciate the Falcons for sure.
>> AJ got a call from Coach Defensky before
you knew that they were going to pick
you.
>> Yeah. Was did he was he able to hide
this? Well, how's his poker face?
>> He hit it. Not he he tried to.
>> See, I've been knowing AJ my whole life,
so I know when the body language, he was
sitting down the whole night, then he
got up.
>> Yeah.
>> He was
>> So, I already I was peeping him a little
bit like, okay, something something
going on.
>> What' you think? What did you think was
happening?
>> What happened me? Yeah, I already knew
it. I already knew at pick 45. I already
knew it.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah.
>> Did you Did you see him actually get a
call? like you have to make big take.
>> No, I can just tell by bro's body
language. He tried to He hit it good
from everybody else, but I can see
through him. I know. I know. I know his
body language.
>> Can you describe just the relationship
the two of you had like since from
child? Kind of you're six years apart.
>> Yeah, we six years. Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. Me and AJ are very close. Talk
every day. Very close. Um that's my dog,
my best friend. And
I love him to death. Hey, like our
relationship, we we uh talk about our
games. Like when I was in college, he
tell me what I need to work on. I tell
him what he need to work on. Just that's
our type of relationship for sure.
>> He referred to you as little bro and I
think he referred to him as twin.
How is
considering the six year gap?
>> Yeah. Um I think it's just an accent
thing in Atlanta. But twin.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. I'm his little brother, but he can
say that. But like the twin thing, I
just think it's an Atlanta accent.
I guess a two-part question. One, did
you get any sleep last night? And two,
when you woke up, did you have a moment
of like, did that really happen?
>> Uh, yeah. I got three hours of sleep.
Three hours. Three hours. When I woke
up, I said, all I said was, "Thank you,
Lord." Like, like, "Let's look at God.
Like, look, look how look how it went."
And I appreciate him for sure.
>> Do you remember AJ's draft night?
>> Yes.
>> First round. Remember what that was
like? And how how could you compare, you
know, seeing him do that to now it's
your turn? Yeah. Um,
you know, when you when you a kid, I was
in 10th grade. I didn't like, yeah, I
see that he happy, but he got emotional,
but I ain't understand. I always I'm
going to cry. I'm going to cry. But me
getting that call yesterday, I I can
feel all the emotions he had. And
that was the biggest thing. Like both of
us getting drafted by the same team.
Come on. Best feeling.
>> Did you have a draft party for the first
round?
>> Yeah, I did.
>> So, what was that like to
have that and not I imagine
disappointing but what was kind of how
how did that whole night?
>> Yeah. Um
no disappointing but more fuel to the
fire. It's all that's all it added to
all it did. Um I knew the next day I was
more calm. I already knew my name was
going to get caught the next day. So you
know woke up with the right mindset
ready to go.
>> How was the hamstring though?
>> It's good. It's good. Yeah. You
>> going to be ready for a rookie mini
camp?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm going to be ready for sure. Do
you think that played a part? I mean,
you never know for sure, but like for
you to go where way past people thought,
like did you did you hear anything from
agent or anybody else that this is
probably the answering or or any other
reason?
>> Um, we we didn't really talk about it
that much. It just know I had my late
pro after that. It was just, man, keep
praying, go get treatment, and we'll see
where you going to go. Um, no, I was had
a little little little nip, but I'm good
now, though. I'm good.
you and AJ are are are very competitive
and now you're going to be teammates for
the first time. Does that increase the
level of competitiveness because now
you're going to be like on the field
with him every single day.
>> Yeah, for sure. For sure. And me and him
going to be going at it too.
>> For sure. I'm going be telling him lock
in. He going to be telling me to lock
in. So all it's going to do is make us
better. Make us better. Two brothers on
the field competing with each other.
It's going to make us better.
I think AJ said more to he's just very
quiet around us. I think he said more to
us last night than he had than he has
also. Did you get the sense that he was
more excited or he's more outwardly
excited for your your success and what
you were doing than he gets for himself
sometimes?
>> Yes. And that's how he always been. He
always been like that. Um he don't show
it a lot. AJ he move quiet but he really
a a loud funny guy. Um, he show every
time I get a compliment, he be the first
one to text me. So, and it made me
emotional last night cuz that hug it
meant a lot to me when me and him hug.
So, for real.
>> Are y are y'all big huggers in general
or was that a was that a rare
occurrence?
>> We always dab each other up. That was
something we don't do. It
>> was a long one, too.
>> Yeah, we did. Long hug.
>> I want to say last year you played like
a 100 snaps inside. I mean, how how
comfortable are you playing inside?
Oh, I'm com I'm comfortable. Same way I
feel outside the same way I feel inside.
>> Is there a change at all?
>> Uh, no,
>> not at all.
>> No, I feel I feel I feel solid at both.
Feel the same way. I can go inside and
not get nervous. I feel I feel good.
>> You enjoy like trying to blitz.
>> Yeah, I love it.
>> Why?
>> Um cuz I'm going to get that
quarterback. That's why they got me. I'm
the one that got to go get him. So
that's why I like doing it.
In the story that Mark wrote by you
guys, I think AJ was saying like he
actually was hoping that you could go
somewhere else to be your own guy. Did
you feel that also or were you like if
all in me equal I'd rather be my brother
or or or kind of whatever however
happens or what was your
>> um
I I can't really say like of course yeah
we don't went to the same high school
same college but I always I always told
AJ like me and you be on the same team
is going to be a blessing that's not
that's not something that happen a lot
so I didn't really like feel no type of
way. Like I said, God is playing. It's
already written. So, I was ready. We was
ready for it for sure.
>> So, your dad's going to finally get that
tattoo of you now.
>> My dad?
>> Yeah.
>> He got it.
>> He got it already.
>> You got to see it.
>> It's tough. Uh probably like a week
after you left.
>> Oh, wow. Okay.
>> He got it.
>> Yeah. He finished it. Okay.
>> You got to see it. You got to see it.
It's hard.
>> He told me that you were you've been
kind of giving them the years,
>> man. He got everybody. He had my two
sisters on there. AJ, I'm the only one
that ain't got no name. So, yeah, I had
I had to tell him something.
>> Oh, there you go.
>> A stat that jumped out at me was five
force fumbles.
>> Yeah.
>> Last year, a school record, I think, for
DBs. Uh, do you think that's a good
answer for those who categorized you as
unders sized?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, they can say the
underside stuff, but like I said, when
we go on that field, it's me against
him. And I'm I'm very good at at
punching at that ball. And I feel like
that's that's one of the best part of my
game, just being able to do that. So
I'm good. Sure.
>> Anything else?
>> All right. Thanks, John.
>> Thank you. Thanks, man.